<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE beans PUBLIC "-//SPRING//DTD BEAN//EN" "http://www.springframework.org/dtd/spring-beans.dtd">

<beans default-autowire="no" default-lazy-init="false" default-dependency-check="none">
	<!-- 
	EvictionTimer implementations are Timer derivations that "intelligently" schedule
	eviction sweeps based on the max age.
	FYI, there are:
	 3600000 milliseconds in one hour
	 86400000 milliseconds in one day
	 604800000 milliseconds in one week
	-->
	<bean 
		id="evictionTimer" 
		class="gov.va.med.imaging.storage.cache.impl.timer.EvictionTimerImpl"
		singleton="true"
		lazy-init="false"
		factory-method="create"
	>
		<constructor-arg>
			<description>
			The constructor arg provided to EvictionTimerImpl maps the maximum age (in milliseconds)
			to the next scheduled sweep.  The map is sorted internally so the lowest value greater than
			the max age is used when scheduling.
			There may be only one key value = "default", which indicates the default scheduling.
			The value specifies the next sweep time, either as an interval or as an
			interval plus a specific Date (if the @ sign is present).
			The interval and specific date time format is yyyy:MM:dd:hh:mm:ss.  
			All fields MUST BE specified and the lengths MUST BE as specified, i.e. month="1" is illegal
			Everything is zero based, including months, i.e. April is 03, January is 00.
			Hours are zero-based on a 24 hour schedule, i.e. 00..23.
			
			If no @ sign is present then the task will be run in the interval specified.
			Examples:
			1.) if key="3600000" and value= "0000:00:00:00:01:00"
			    then for tasks with an aging of less than one hour (3600000 milliseconds) run the task every minute.
			2.) if key="86400000" and value= "0000:00:00:00:01:00"
			    then for tasks with an aging of less than one day (86400000 milliseconds) run the task every hour.
			3.) if key="60000" and value= "0000:00:00:00:00:36"
			    then for tasks with an aging of less than one minute (60000 milliseconds) run the task every 36 seconds.

			If the @ sign is present then the task will be run in the delta specified, at the specified time.
			Examples:
			1.) if key="3600000" and value= "0000:00:00:00:01:00@0000:00:00:00:00:20"
			    then for tasks with an aging of less than one hour (3600000 milliseconds) run the task every minute on the 20 second boundary
			2.) if key="default" and value= "0000:00:01:00:00:00@0000:00:00:03:00:00"
			    then for tasks with an aging greater than any explicitly defined run the task every day at 3AM
			3.) if key="default" and value= "0001:00:00:00:00:00@0000:04:07:03:23:34"
			    then for tasks with an aging greater than any explicitly defined run the task every year at 3:23:34 on April 7
			If the @ sign is present then the magnitutude of the boundary (the right of the @ sign) MUST BE less than the magnitude of
			the interval (the left of the @ sign).  i.e. scheduling something to run every minute at 3AM will result in an error, scheduling
			something to run every 10 minutes on a 2 minute boundary will also fail (... okay, it should work but geeze ain't this enough!).
			The difference must be between components (i.e. hours/minutes or days/hours).
			</description>
			<map>
				<entry key="60000"><value>0000:00:00:00:00:10</value></entry>			<!-- if less than a minute then next 10 seconds, this is mostly here for testing -->
				<entry key="3600000"><value>0000:00:00:00:01:00</value></entry>			<!-- if less than an hour then next minute -->
				<entry key="86400000"><value>0000:00:00:01:00:00</value></entry>		<!-- if less than a day then next hour -->
				<entry key="default"><value>0000:00:01:00:00:00@0000:00:00:03:00:00</value></entry>		<!-- else, run it at 3AM -->
			</map>
		</constructor-arg>
	</bean>
</beans>